Guide to the Interfaith Center on Corporate Responsibility records,
Rare Book and Manuscript Library Columbia University Libraries
Interfaith Center on Corporate Responsibility Records,
1966-2011
Interfaith Center on Corporate Responsibility.
137.5 linear ft. (110 records boxes)
Columbia University. Rare Book and Manuscript Library New York, NY. 10027
HR#0009
8429461
The Interfaith Center on Corporate Responsibility (ICCR) is a coalition of predominantly faith based institutions that are committed to socially responsible investing. The strength of the records lies in their documentation of the ICCR’s programs, its work on individual issues, and its work with individual corporations and the U.S. Security and Exchanges Commission (SEC).
Historical Note
The Interfaith Center on Corporate Responsibility (ICCR) grew out of an interest in socially responsible investing that arose from concerns of clergy that churches might be profiting from the Vietnam War through their investments. In 1971, the Episcopal Church and six other protestant denominations formed the Interfaith Committee on Social Responsibility in Investments (ICSRI), which would allow for the group to share information and coordinate efforts to press for corporate change through their collective investments. During that same year, the Episcopal Church filed the first religious-sponsored shareholder resolution with General Motors requesting that the company withdraw its operations from apartheid South Africa. The committee soon filed additional resolutions on other social issues using similar strategies.
The organization expanded during the 1970s. The ICSRI’s membership grew quickly, and within a few years was joined by Jewish investors and the National Catholic Coalition for Responsible Investment. In 1973, the ICSRI merged with the Corporate Information Center (CIC) to form the Interfaith Center on Corporate Responsibility (ICCR). The CIC had been founded in 1971 as a research project within the National Council of Churches (NCC), and produced the Corporate Examiner newsletter and other research reports on corporate responsibility. The two organizations had worked closely together, and the merger allowed for the ICSRI, which focused on coordination and strategy, to form one organization with the CIC, which focused on research, education, and producing information.
The ICCR has expanded and diversified both its membership and its strategies since its founding. Although the ICCR began as an alliance of faith-based organizations, it expanded its membership to include non-faith based organizations interested in social justice. In 1982, Calvert Group joined the ICCR as its first non-faith based member, and unions, pension funds, and other groups joined the ICCR throughout the 1980s. The ICCR also expanded its original approach of filing resolutions and attending shareholder meetings to engaging in direct dialog with corporations, as well as employing letter writing campaigns, and other strategies.
The ICCR’s work has expanded and changed to engage new issues over time. During the 1970s and 1980s, its work focused on several issues including apartheid, nutrition and the irresponsible distribution of infant formula, equal opportunity employment, diversity, equal access to capital, military profiteering, negative portrayals of women and minorities in advertising, political contributions, and the environmental impact of strip mining. During the 1990s and 2000s, the ICCR also worked on issues related to the corporate governance and policy, the environment and energy, militarism and violence, sweat shop labor, tobacco, and other human rights issues.
Today, the ICCR is comprised of nearly 300 organizations with collective investments of over $100 billion, which continues to influence corporate policy on environmental, social, and economic issues.
Scope and Content
The records of the Interfaith Center on Corporate Responsibility (ICCR) primarily document the work of the center's staff, although the collection also includes records relating to the activities of its governing board and individual member organizations. The strength of the collection lies in its documentation of ICCR's programs, its work on issues, and its work with individual corporations and the SEC.
The collection includes many records related to programs and issues coordinated through the ICCR, which originate from both Program Directors and Executive Directors. There is extensive documentation of the ICCR's work on issues related to apartheid South Africa and the responsible distribution of infant formula. In addition, there are records documenting work on issues related to the environment, corporate governance, discrimination and equality, health, labor, militarism, and violence. These records include action and campaign materials, correspondence, minutes, meeting files, reports, and working group materials, as well as research materials and general subject files.
ICCR's work with individual companies is also well-documented in the records. The company files include materials on companies, their business practices, and proxy resolutions filed by ICCR members. Some files also include information requests, clippings, and communications with other entities such as the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC).
The collection also documents ICCR's work with the SEC. These records include documentation of ICCR's advocacy work on SEC policies and rule change proposals that relate to its work, such those related to as corporate disclosure, proxy rules, and shareholder rights and resolutions. The ICCR also works with the SEC on issues related to its shareholder resolutions, and this work is documented through correspondence, information on the resolutions, and responses to corporate challenges.
There is some information on members and subscribers in the collection. Much of the communication with members, particularly on issues and resolutions, is with those files. In addition, the ICCR's staff was often copied on members' direct communication with companies and other entities. There are some membership files, which include information on the member organizations, pledges, mailings, and subscriptions, but only for 1995-2002.
Coverage is less comprehensive for high-level administrative records of the ICCR. The collection does not include any large sets of executive records, per se, rather, the executive records in the collection primarily relate to work with specific issues and companies. In addition, there is limited coverage of the activities of ICCR's governing board. The collection includes board mailings (1993-2000), and while these include some memos and minutes, there are no other records related to the board's regular activities in the collection. However, there is coverage of annual planning meetings (1975-1995). Initially, ICCR held annual long range planning meetings or retreats. By the early 1980s, these meetings became Annual General Meetings. These records include minutes, questionnaires, evaluations, reports, and development papers.
Coverage of publicity materials is also limited within the collection. There are files of clippings and press releases from the 1970s, but they are not well-organized. In addition, some material exists that relates to the 15th, 20th, and 40th anniversaries. Otherwise, there is no comprehensive coverage of publicity or promotional materials. There is good, but not comprehensive, coverage of major publications, such as the Corporate Examiner and the Proxy Resolutions Book.
There is also very little audiovisual material in the records; there are a few audio and video recordings, and no photograph files.
Arrangement
This collection is arranged in eleven series and several subseries:
Series I. Early History, 1971-1982
Series II. ICCR Governing Board, 1993-2000
Series III. Annual General Meetings, 1975-1995, 2008
Series IV. Issues and Programs, 1966-2010
Subseries IV.1. Corporate Governance, Equality, and Indigenous Issues, 1971-2009 [Bulk Dates: 1989-2007]
Subseries IV.2. Environment and Energy, 1979-1980, 1999-2010
Subseries IV.3. Human Rights/Labor Rights/Global Accountability Programs, 1996-2011
Subseries IV.4. Infant Formula, 1972-1993
Subseries IV.5. Militarism and Violence, 1990-2007
Subseries IV.6. South Africa, 1966-1996
Subseries IV.7. Tobacco, 1985-1999
Series V. Company Files, 1966-2009
Series VI. U.S. Security and Exchanges Commission (SEC) Files, 1972-2007 [Bulk Dates: 1990-2004]
Series VII. Publications, 1974-2011
Series VIII. Member & Subscriber Services, 1995-2003
Subseries VIII.1. Associate and Subscriber Files, 1995-2003
Subseries VIII.2. Membership Files, 1995-2002
Series IX. Communications and Publicity, 1971-1999 [Bulk Dates: 1971-1979, 1996]
Series X. Audiovisual Materials, 2000-2002, Undated.
Series XI. General Organizational Records, 1986-2011
Subjects
Corporate Information Center of the National Council of Churches; Interfaith Center on Corporate Responsibility; Interfaith Committee on Social Responsibility in Investments; Business ethics; Church and industry; Church and social problems; Investments--Moral and ethical aspects; Investments--Social Aspects; Proxy Statements; Social Responsibility of Business; Clippings; Corporation Reports; Correspondence; Newsletters
Access Restrictions
This collection is located off-site. You will need to request this material at least twenty-four (24) hours in advance to use the collection in the Rare Book and Manuscript Library reading room.
This collection has no restrictions.
Acquisition
Interfaith Center on Corporate Responsibility, Gift, March 3, 2011, 2010-2011-M064
Finding aid in repository and online.
- Series I: Early History, 1971-1982
  This series contains files relating to the early history of the Interfaith Committee on Social Responsibility in Investments (ICSRI), the Corporate Information Center (CIC), and their merger to form the Interfaith Center on Corporate Responsibility (ICCR). The series also contains material related to early work on issues such as mining, eco-justice, and South Africa. The records include clippings, correspondence, minutes, proposals, and reports.
  - Early Organizational Files
    - The Church and the Transnational Corporation (TNC), 1972-1975 (Box 26, Folder 1)
    - Corporate Information Center (CIC)
      - General, 1971-1972 (Box 26, Folder 2)
      - Ad Hoc Proposal (Master Copy), 1971 (Box 26, Folder 3)
      - Alternative Investments, 1975 (Box 26, Folder 4)
      - Business, 1972-1973 (2 Folders) (Box 26, Folder 5)
      - Church Project Press Conference, 1974 (Box 26, Folder 6)
      - Proposal for Corporate Information Center (CIC) and Progress Reports, 1971 (Box 26, Folder 7)
    - Corporate Information Center (CIC) and Interfaith Committee on Social Responsibility In Investments (ICSRI) Merger into the Interfaith Center on Corporate Responsibility (ICCR), 1973 (2 Folders) (Box 26, Folder 8 to 9)
    - Interfaith Ecumenical Committee, 1971-1973 (2 Folders) (Box 26, Folder 10 to 11)
    - Interfaith Committee on Social Responsibility In Investment (ICSRI)
      - General, 1972-1973 (2 Folders) (Box 26, Folder 12 to 13)
      - Mailings, 1973 (Box 26, Folder 14)
      - Minutes (Masters), 1973 (Box 26, Folder 15)
      - Research Subcommittee, 1972 (Box 26, Folder 16)
    - Interfaith Center on Corporate Responsibility (ICCR), 1974 (Box 26, Folder 17)
  - Early Subject Files
    - Corporate Responsibility
      - General, 1980, 1982 (2 Folders) (Box 26, Folder 18)
      - Packet (United Methodist Church), 1974, 1977 (2 Folders) (Box 26, Folder 19)
    - Eco-Justice, 1972-1973 (Box 26, Folder 20)
    - Eco-Justice Task Force, 1973-1974 (Box 26, Folder 21)
    - Mining
      - Puerto Rico Copper Mining and Annual Meeting Resolutions, 1971 (Box 26, Folder 22)
      - Wise, Virginia--Hearings, Summary, and Response, 1974 (2 Folders) (Box 26, Folder 23 to 24)
      - Press Work Notes on Strip-mining Church Panel, 1974 (Box 26, Folder 25)
    - Significant Memos to South Africa Interest Group, 1980 (Box 26, Folder 26)
    - Western Coal Development (Report for ICCR by Mike Ross), 1976 (Box 26, Folder 27)
- Series II: ICCR Governing Board, 1993-2000
  This series consists of board mailings. The set is incomplete for both 1996 and 2000. The mailings include memos, minutes, and informational materials that were mailed to the board.
  - Mailings
    - 1993-1995 (Box 101)
    - 1996-2000 May (Box 100)
- Series III: Annual General Meetings, 1975-1995, 2008
  ICCR’s Annual General Meetings grew out of Long Range Planning Meetings and Retreats that began in the 1970s. The records include evaluations, minutes, questionnaires, reports, and development papers (often gathered into “resource books”) on various issues which include rationales for the program, objectives, and action plans.
  - 1975 (2 Folders) (Box 28, Folder 1 to 2)
  - 1976
    - General (2 Folders) (Box 28, Folder 3 to 4)
    - Evaluation of Long-Range Planning (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - 1977 (4 Folders) (Box 28, Folder 6 to 9)
  - 1978
    - General (Box 28, Folder 10)
    - Design Team (Box 28, Folder 11)
    - Resource Book (Box 28, Folder 12)
  - 1979
    - General (Box 28, Folder 13)
    - Design Team (Box 28, Folder 14)
  - 1980
    - General (Box 28, Folder 15)
    - Resource Book (Box 28, Folder 16)
  - 1981
    - General (Box 28, Folder 17)
    - Resource Book, 1981-1982 (Box 28, Folder 18)
  - 1982
    - General (Box 28, Folder 19)
    - Resource Book, 1982-1983 (Box 28, Folder 20)
  - 1983
    - General (Box 28, Folder 21)
    - Report on Year’s Work, 1982-1983 (Box 28, Folder 22)
    - Resource Book (Box 28, Folder 23)
  - 1984 (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - 1985 (2 Folders) (Box 27, Folder 2 to 3)
  - 1986 (3 Folders) (Box 27, Folder 4 to 6)
  - 1987 (2 Folders) (Box 27, Folder 7 to 8)
  - 1988
    - General (Box 27, Folder 9)
    - Planning Committee (Box 27, Folder 10)
  - 1989 (Box 27, Folder 11)
  - 1990
    - General (Box 27, Folder 12)
    - Priorities Survey (Box 27, Folder 13)
  - 1991
    - General (Box 27, Folder 14)
    - Evaluation Questionnaire
      - General (Box 27, Folder 15)
      - Report (Box 27, Folder 16)
      - Original Surveys (Completed) (10 Folders) (Box 27, Folder 17)
  - 1992-1993 (3 Folders) (Box 27, Folder 18 to 20)
  - 1994 (Box 27, Folder 21)
  - 1995 (Box 27, Folder 22)
  - 2008 (Box 64, Folder 9)
- Series IV: Issues and Programs, 1966-2010
  This series consists of files related to programs and issues coordinated through the ICCR. Most of these records originate from the program directors that were responsible for their management, however, some related records were also kept by Executive Directors. These records include action and campaign materials, correspondence, minutes, meeting files, reports, and working group materials, as well as research materials such as clippings, company information, images, and reports.
  - Subseries IV.1. Corporate Governance, Equality, and Indigenous Issues, 1971-2009
    - A&P, 1993-2001 (Box 104, Folder 9)
    - ABC, 1991-2000 (Box 104, Folder 10)
    - Abercrombie and Fitch, 1999 (Box 104, Folder 11)
    - Alberton, 1993-1999 (Box 104, Folder 12)
    - American Brands, 1994-1997 (Box 104, Folder 13)
    - American Eagle, 2002 (Box 104, Folder 14)
    - American Express, 1999-2000 (Box 104, Folder 15)
    - American International Group (AIG), 1996-1999 (Box 97, Folder 5)
    - American Standard/Trane, 2005-2006 (Box 104, Folder 16)
    - Anheuser-Busch Companies, 1997 (Box 97, Folder 6)
    - Apache, 1994 (Box 104, Folder 17)
    - BP, 1993-2006 (Box 104, Folder 18)
    - Caterpillar, 1993 (Box 104, Folder 19)
    - CBS, 1992-1999 (Box 104, Folder 20)
    - Cendant, 2005-2006 (Box 104, Folder 21)
    - Circuit City, 1996-2003 (Box 104, Folder 22)
    - Citibank, 2009 (Box 105, Folder 1)
    - Coca Cola, 1981-2009 (2 Folders) (Box 105, Folder 2 to 3)
    - Corporate Governance
      - General, 1993-2007 (2 Folders) (Box 97, Folder 14)
      - Content Ratings, 2002-2006 (Box 54, Folder 17)
      - Survey on Corporate Board Inclusiveness, 2008 (Box 97, Folder 17)
      - Various Papers, circa 2001-2010 (Box 97, Folder 15)
    - Costco, 2003-2009 (Box 105, Folder 4)
    - Debt
      - General, 1983-1995 (2 Folders) (Box 14, Folder 18 to 19)
      - Debt Interest Group, 1990-1993 (2 Folders) (Box 14, Folder 24 to 25)
      - Global Finance--50 Years is Enough Beyond the Debt Campaign, 1994 (Box 14, Folder 23)
      - Latin American Agribusiness Development Corporation (S.A. LAAD), 1976 (Box 14, Folder 21)
      - Nicaragua Debt--Private Banks, 1994 (Box 14, Folder 20)
      - Nigeria--Miscellaneous, 1995-1997 (Box 14, Folder 26)
    - Executive Compensation--General
      - 1992 (Box 14, Folder 17)
      - 2007 (Box 14, Folder 18)
      - 2006-2007 (Box 97, Folder 16)
    - Exxon, 1972-1999 (Box 105, Folder 5)
    - Federal Glass Ceiling Commission, 1995 (Box 30, Folder 33)
    - General Electric (GE)/NBC, 1982-2000 (Box 105, Folder 6)
    - Halliburton, 1995-1998 (Box 105, Folder 7)
    - Home Depot, 1996-2002 (Box 105, Folder 8)
    - Honeywell, 1994-2007 (Box 105, Folder 9)
    - ICCR Special Event on Violence Proposal, 2006-2007 (Box 97, Folder 18)
    - Indigenous Peoples
      - General, 1999-2004 (Box 97, Folder 19)
      - Photographs of Examples, 1990s-2000s (Box 105, Folder 19)
    - Intel--Executive Compensation, 1995-1996 (Box 105, Folder 10)
    - Kmart, 1989-1999 (Box 102, Folder 1)
    - Microsoft, 1995-1996 (Box 105, Folder 11)
    - PepsiCo, 1997-2000 (Box 105, Folder 12)
    - Proctor & Gamble, 1993-1998 (Box 105, Folder 13)
    - Sears, 1986-1998 (Box 102, Folder 2)
    - Six Flags, 2007 (Box 97, Folder 7)
    - Target, 1996-2002 (Box 105, Folder 14)
    - Texaco
      - Annual Meetings, 1971-2000 (Box 98, Folder 1)
      - Annual Reports, 1991-1999 (Box 98, Folder 2)
      - Court Case
        - Court Papers, circa 1992 (Box 98, Folder 3)
        - 16 Points, 1992-1995 (Box 98, Folder 4)
        - General, 1995-2001 (5 Folders) (Box 98, Folder 5 to 9)
      - Literature on Diversity and Equal Opportunity, 1993-1998 (Box 98, Folder 10)
      - Resolutions, 1979-1998 (2 Folders) (Box 98, Folder 11 to 12)
    - Time Warner
      - General, 1993-1999 (Box 97, Folder 8)
      - Executive Compensation, 1996 (Box 97, Folder 9)
      - Media Violence, 1999 (Box 97, Folder 10)
    - Tootsie Roll, 2001 (Box 97, Folder 11)
    - U.S. Airlines, 1993-2007 (Box 97, Folder 12)
    - Walmart, 1992-2000 (Box 105, Folder 15)
    - W.R. Grace--Executive Compensation, 1992-1994 (Box 105, Folder 16)
    - Xerox, 1994-2001 (Box 97, Folder 13)
  - Subseries IV.2. Environment and Energy, 1979-1980, 1999-2010
    - General
      - Environment and Energy (E&E)--Strategic Plan, 2008-2009 (Box 64, Folder 8)
    - Abbott Laboratories, 2009 (Box 85, Folder 1)
    - Anadarko Petroleum Corporation, 2004 (Box 85, Folder 2)
    - Apache Corporation, 2004 (Box 85, Folder 3)
    - Applebee’s International Inc., 2003 (Box 85, Folder 4)
    - Chevron (CVX)--Ecuador Resolution, 2006 (Box 77, Folder 1)
    - Chevron Texaco Corporation, 2005 (Box 85, Folder 5)
    - Citigroup, 2007 (Box 85, Folder 6)
    - Coal News, 2006-2009 (Box 85, Folder 28)
    - Coca-Cola Company, 2003-2004 (Box 85, Folder 7)
    - Conoco Phillips, 2003-2004 (Box 85, Folder 8)
    - Dow Chemical Company, 2003 (Box 85, Folder 9)
    - DuPont Company, 2004 (Box 85, Folder 10)
    - Eastman Chemical Company, 2000 (Box 85, Folder 11)
    - Environment Report
      - Investment Management, 2001-2004 (Box 77, Folder 2)
      - Paper Industry, 2010 (Box 77, Folder 3)
    - Environment Reporting
      - Accounting Issues, 2002-2004 (Box 77, Folder 4)
      - Compliance, 2003-2006 (Box 77, Folder 5)
      - Rose Petition / Climate Petition, circa 2002 (Box 77, Folder 6)
    - Environmental Justice
      - Environmental Justice: A Case Study of ICCR’s Engagement with Synagro-NYOFCo, 2008 (Box 77, Folder 7)
      - Conoco Phillips Refineries, 2006-2010 (Box 77, Folder 8)
      - Exxon-Mobil (Refinieries), 2005-2007 (Box 77, Folder 9)
      - Oil Refineries, 2005-2007 (Box 77, Folder 10)
      - Place: Notes, 2008-2009 (Box 64, Folder 5)
    - Environmental Management Systems (EMS), 2003-2004 (Box 85, Folder 29)
    - Exelon, 2008-2009 (Box 85, Folder 12)
    - Extraction Industries
      - General, 2003-2007 (2 Folders) (Box 85, Folder 30-30a)
      - Chevron-Texaco, 1999-2002 (Box 77, Folder 11)
      - Conoco Phillips (Burlington Resources), 2004-2009 (Box 77, Folder 12)
      - Gold Mining, 2003-2006 (Box 77, Folder 13)
      - Oil and Gas Sector, 2003-2007 (Box 77, Folder 14)
      - Shell Oil, 2001-2007 (Box 77, Folder 15)
      - World Bank--Extractive Industries Review (EIR), 2003-2006 (Box 85, Folder 31)
    - Exxon Mobil Corporation (Energy), 2005 (Box 85, Folder 13)
    - Ford Motor Company, 2004 (Box 85, Folder 14)
    - Free Prior Informed Consent (FPIC)--Advisory Panel, 2006-2007 (Box 77, Folder 16)
    - General Electric, 2002 (Box 85, Folder 15)
    - General Motors Corporation, 2004 (Box 85, Folder 16)
    - Georgia-Pacific, 2003 (Box 85, Folder 17)
    - Global Principles--Benchmarks, 2003 (Box 78, Folder 1)
    - Global Warming
      - General Background, 2002-2003 (Box 63, Folder 1)
      - Air Emissions--Reports, 2002-2004 (Box 75, Folder 1)
      - American Power Company
        - General, 2003-2009 (Box 75, Folder 2)
        - Dialogue, 2010 (Box 75, Folder 3)
      - Carbon Disclosure Project, 2003 (Box 63, Folder 2)
      - Cinergy, 2002-2005 (Box 75, Folder 4)
      - Climate Actions by Companies, circa 2007 (Box 36, Folder 1)
      - Climate Leaders, 2006 (Box 63, Folder 3)
      - Company Reports (Utilities), 2004-2006 (Box 75, Folder 5)
      - Economic Effects, 2001-2007 (Box 63, Folder 4)
      - Exxon Mobil
        - General, 2004-2009 (Box 75, Folder 6)
        - Dialogues, 2003-2006 (Box 75, Folder 7)
        - Reports, 2004-2007 (Box 75, Folder 8)
      - Forests--Carbon Sequestration, 2005-2008 (Box 36, Folder 2)
      - Greenhouse Gases (GHG)
        - Investment Risks and Impacts, 1996-2006 (Box 63, Folder 5)
        - Registries, 2003-2004 (Box 36, Folder 3)
        - Reporting Protocol, 2003 (Box 36, Folder 4)
      - ICCR Environment and Energy Program, Undated (Box 63, Folder 6)
        (Printout of presentation slides)
      - Impacts (Health, Society, Economy, Etc.), 2005-2007 (Box 36, Folder 5)
      - Institute for Civil Society Grant, 2001-2006 (Box 63, Folder 7)
      - Investment Network on Climate Risk (INCR) / CERES, 2005 (Box 36, Folder 6)
      - Manufacturing, 2005 (Box 75, Folder 9)
      - Policy Statements--Faith Based Organizations, 2005-2007 (Box 36, Folder 7)
      - Real Estate, 2002 (Box 75, Folder 10)
      - Religion and Environment, 2005-2008 (Box 36, Folder 8)
      - Reports on Climate, 2002-2005 (Box 63, Folder 8)
      - Research from Companies
        - ERB Institute, 2007 (Box 36, Folder 21)
        - Innovest, circa 2003 (Box 36, Folder 22)
        - Trucost
          - General, 2007 (Box 36, Folder 23)
          - ICCR Data Partnership, 2005-2009 (Box 36, Folder 24)
          - Research Papers, 2005-2006 (Box 36, Folder 25)
      - Retail Sector, 2002-2003 (Box 75, Folder 11)
      - Southern Company
        - General, 2005-2008 (Box 75, Folder 12)
        - Dialogue, 2003-2008 (2 Folders) (Box 75, Folder 13)
      - Unocal Dialogue, 2003-2006 (Box 75, Folder 14)
      - U.S. Climate Action Report, 2007 (Box 63, Folder 9)
      - Utilities
        - General, 2003-2008 (Box 75, Folder 15)
        - Media, 2003-2008 (Box 75, Folder 16)
        - Regulation--Clean Air Act (CAA); Mercury, 2002-2008 (Box 75, Folder 17)
      - Xcel Energy, 2004-2006 (Box 75, Folder 18)
    - Global Warming Shareholders’ Campaign (GWC or GWSC)
      - General, 2007-2008 (2 Folders) (Box 36, Folder 9)
      - American Gas Association, 2008 (Box 63, Folder 10)